What's up, big fella?
>> Hey, how you doing?
>> Are you ready to officially become a
Minnesota Viking?
>> Yes, sir. Let's do it.
>> You do your part and uh the sky's the
limit for you, man.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you so much.
>> Byebye,
>> Caleb. Congrats, man.
>> Thank you, coach. Thank you.
>> It sounds awful quiet, man. You with
your family? What do you Where you at?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I got I got like a 100
people with
>> You want to hear some of thoseund
people, man? You're a Minnesota Viking.
>> Get over here.
>> There we go. There we go.
>> Hey, I just want to tell you, man, the
belief we have in you in this building
um is real. Throughout this whole
process, you did your part and we're
going to do ours for you. Help you
become the best version of yourself,
man. Can't wait to get you here. Okay.
Thanks.
>> Congratulations.
>> Good. I'm ready.
>> You ready to go?
>> All right. Let's get the dog. Let's get
the Let's get the snakes. Let's get the
chameleon. Let's get everybody packed
up.
>> Minnesotabody.
>> Yeah. Bring Br all bring them all. And I
know you're going to bring your best,
too. So,
>> we're excited to We're excited to get
you here.
>> Look at that.
[applause]
>> We're going to take you here, man. We're
excited. We'd love to visit with you up
here in Minnesota and uh we're going to
bring you up here and we're excited to
have you,
>> man. I can't wait. I've been waiting my
whole life for this,
>> Jake. Congratulations, man.
>> Thank you so much. Appreciate you. Yeah,
I hope uh I hope you felt it, you know,
on your visit how much love we got for
you. We got a ton of, you know, upside
in you, but also just your your ability
to be one of those guys that come in
here as a smart, tough, love football
kind of guy, our kind of guy. Um, and
those guys tend to do pretty well here,
and that's exactly what you're going to
do. All right.
>> Yes, sir. No doubt. Can't wait for the
opportunity.
>> Yeah. Congrats to you and your family
and and can't wait to uh get a chance to
get you up here. Okay.
>> I'm excited. I can't wait to get up
there and start working. Coach
>> Big Citrus, what's up?
>> What's happening, boys, man?
>> You ready to rock, man?
>> Hell yeah. Then what, man? We ready to
roll.
>> The best news is, man, we got uh we got
you and uh Caleb Banks coming in here
together to change our defensive front.
How about that?
>> Come on, man. It's going to be a problem
for real, though. I'm telling you.
[laughter]
>> Hell yeah, man. Well, hey, I'm excited.
Uh congrats to you, your family. Uh what
a uh dream come true, man. You're a
Minnesota Viking. We're fired up.
>> Hey, how you doing?
>> Welcome to Minnesota.
>> Yeah, I appreciate it.
>> You're gonna look good in purple.
>> Uh I think purple's kind of really my
color.
>> I was just going to say it's a smooth
transition. Here's Coach O'Connell.
Congratulations.
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> Caleb, congrats, man.
>> I appreciate it, coach.
>> Yeah, man. You're fired up. I like
hearing that. We are uh we are fired up
here to get you. We've been holding out
uh watching these picks come off the
board just hoping we wouldn't see your
name and and uh couldn't get we didn't
waste a lot of time to turn this one in.
Man, we're fired up. Can't wait to get
you here and get you with our guys.
>> Jacobe, what's up, man?
>> You should have just camped out here
from top 30.
>> Jacobe, congrats, man.
>> You there, man?
>> Oh, I got you. Enjoy this moment, man.
The emotion is real.
>> Hey, just know something, man. We uh we
are so fired up to get you here. You
came here, impressed the heck out of
everybody in this whole building. We
know you're going to make our whole
building better, man, with who you are
and what you are as a player, a person.
You're going to uh you're going to love
playing for this guy right here. I know
you know who he is, man. Here's Brian
Flores.
>> Looking forward to to working with you,
spending time with you. and growing with
you and um when you get here, man, we
just need we want your best. We know
we'll get that. So, congratulations,
>> Max. What's up, man? Congratulations.
>> Thank you, sir. Fired up.
>> Yeah. You ready to go?
>> Yes, sir. You know it. You know it.
>> We uh we got a whole room full of people
that uh fell in love with you on the
visit and uh you're going to help us,
man. You're going to help our team. Love
everything about who you are as a player
and person. And um we talk about Vikings
fits a lot and you are absolutely that
my friend. Can't wait to get you here.
>> Yes sir. Fired up for a coach. Fired up.
>> All right. I got Coach Modkins for you
here in a second.
>> Coach M. My guy. Let's go. [laughter]
>> Congratulations, man.
>> Thank you. I appreciate you, coach.
>> Charles, man. Congrats.
>> I appreciate it, dog. Man, so good. Your
voice sound like better than any melody
I heard, man. [laughter]
>> That's the first time in my life
anybody's told me my voice sounded like
a melody. Thank you for that, man.
>> Hey, right on time, man.
>> You just made You just [laughter] made
my whole day right there. I hope I hope
we made yours. We're fired up, bro.
>> Oh, yeah, man. This is divine
interaction right here, dog. You
[laughter] know the the other teams,
man. They drafted dogs, but John just
got a beast, man. I'm telling you.
>> Hey, I'm gonna hold you to that, man.
>> I'm telling you.
>> I'm gonna hold you to that.
>> Oh, yeah. We gonna walk through the door
and run straight through it, man.
[laughter]
>> Deon, how you doing, my man?
>> Doing good. how you doing?
>> I I I know it's been a long couple of
days, but uh you're you're in the place
that you're meant to be in, and we could
not be more excited to have you and the
story that's going to be written ahead
with you, it's going to be incredible.
So, I'm going to give you Coach
O'Connell, but congratulations. We're
going to take you with this pick. Okay,
>> I got you. Thank you. Appreciate it.
>> Demon, congrats, man.
>> Appreciate it, coach.
>> We get to go to work together and uh you
know, make this thing the best thing to
ever happen to you. All right.
>> Yeah. Yes, sir. Coach, let's do it. I'm
happy.
>> Gavin, how are you?
I'm good. So,
>> congratulations, my man. You ready to
come to Minnesota?
>> I would love that.
>> You are everything that we are looking
for in a Viking. Smart toughs love
football and uh looking forward to
getting you here, my man.
>> I appreciate that.
>> We know you got all the, you know, all
the ability to do it. You know,
everything inside your heart and your
mind and we're going to coach you up,
man. We're going to buy in and and we're
all in on you. So, get here and get
ready to rock and roll.
>> Yes, sir. I really appreciate it.
>> Yeah. Congrats to you and your family,
brother.
>> I appreciate it. Thank you so much.